Israel Molestina

1427 Fitzwater st F1 — Philadelphia, PA, 19146 (704) 929-1620 — molestinaisrael@gmail.com Portfolio — https://israel-molestina.github.io/

 $Linked In - \underline{\textit{https://www.linkedin.com/in/israel-molestina-8546aa1ba/} \ || \ Git Hub - \underline{\textit{https://github.com/Israel-Molestina-8546aa1ba/}} \ || \ Git$

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Hard working product manager with a background in customer service and developed skills necessary to deliver client satisfaction through personable leadership. As a first-generation immigrant, I strive to bring diversity into all my workspaces. Worked my way through college and went from a barback to the manager of a high-end cocktail lounge within a year. There I led my team to create seasonal craft cocktails and provide clients with a welcoming and personable experience, while also increasing profit margins for the business. Recently earned a certificate in full stack development from the University of Pennsylvania, enhancing my skills in responsive web design, JavaScript, React.js, Node.js, and MySQL. Excited to bring my leadership skills into the technology sector and continue leading teams to success.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA

PENN LPS coding Bootcamp

Philadelphia, PA

Dec 2020 - June 2021

UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA AT ASHEVILLE

Completed coursework towards B.S. Business

Asheville, NC

Jan 2017 - Mar 2018

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

The Imperial Life

Bar Manager/Lead Bartender

Asheville, NC

Dec 2018 - Mar 2020

- Compiling and purchasing weekly liquor orders upwards of \$2,500
- Integral in event planning and community/charitable initiatives surrounding the bar
- Managed schedule for 8 employees
- Assisting with wait staff management and customer service
- Menu preparation and creation

Asheville Realty Group

Asheville, NC

Dec 2017 – Dec 2018

- Buyers and Sellers Agent
- Managed listings for properties valuing over \$100,000+
- Oversaw referral process for properties totaling \$300,000+
- Performed administrative duties such as showcasing available properties, communicating with potential clients, and maintaining property and facilities.

PROJECTS

Realtor

Movie Roulette 2021

A browser-based application that takes in user input and suggests a movie based on that input. The application allows the user to rate, take notes and save the movies they've watched, adding it to a watched movies list. It was built using JavaScript and two API's.

• https://israel-molestina.github.io/Movie-Roulette/

Weather Dashboard 2021

A Weather Dashboard App that allows the user to enter a city and displays that city's current and future weather conditions. The cities entered are then displayed on a search list so the user can easily search them again.

https://israel-molestina.github.io/weather-dashboard/

Day Planner 2021

A Day Planner that allows users to input tasks for the workday. It was built using jQuery and the Luxon Library. It also takes advantage of the user's local storage to store tasks.

• https://israel-molestina.github.io/calender-scheduler/

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Technical:

• HTML | CSS | JavaScript | jQuery

Interpersonal:

- Fluency in Spanish
- Excellent multitasker
- Interpersonal and communication skills
- Managerial and conflict resolution skills
- Budget management